LAUREN KROHN

ATTORNEY



CONTACT

856.313.8755

✓ laurenkrohn@gmail.com

in LinkedIn.com/in/Lauren-Krohn

github.com/atlas-lauren

336 Pemberton St, Philadelphia, PA

EDUCATION

JURIS DOCTORATE,

Rutgers University School of Law 2011 — 2014

BACHELOR'S DEGREE,

History, Political Science & Spanish
University of Delaware
2005 — 2009

FINTECH BOOT CAMP,

University of Pennsylvania 2022

SKILLS

| Technical

Coding Languages: Python, Solidity, Cypher

GitHub

Visual Studio Code

SmartSheet Super User

Relativity

iManage

Neo4j

Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint

Adobe Acrobat

SUMMARY

After 4 years immersed in one of the most complex environmental cases before the federal bar I have a strong grasp on translation: environmental data into legal arguments, legalese into English, raw technology into usable systems. My boots-on-the-ground litigation experience has given me a healthy appreciation for designing efficient systems. This year I completed a coding bootcamp to learn cutting edge techniques in data management, machine learning, and blockchain technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ASSOCIATE, ENVIRONMENTAL LITIGATION

Archer & Greiner, PC | 2017 - present

Archer's Environmental Litigation practice group handles complex environmental litigation for industry leaders, including OxyChem, ExxonMobil, and Hess. Since 2018 my practice has focused on a multi-party federal matter with over \$2 billion at stake (Occidental Chemical Corp. v. 21st Century Fox America, Inc.). We represent the sole plaintiff seeking contribution under CERCLA from over 100 corporations.

- I am an integral player in a team of attorneys handling all aspects of complex federal litigation against 100+ defendants, including drafting pleadings, written discovery, and motions; analyzing discovery responses and document productions; preparing for oral arguments and monthly conferences; and depositions of executives, technical employees, and experts.
- Interface with environmental and corporate forensic experts and manage expert tasks and budgets.
- Manage an internal team of two associate attorneys and three paralegals.
- Designed and built a case management solution in SmartSheet to index and retrieve voluminous correspondence and documents. This system is currently being used to facilitate work across three law firms.
- Designed a document review protocol and managed team of over 40 lawyers in review of 300.000 documents.

ASSOCIATE, CORPORATE TRANSACTIONS

Archer & Greiner, PC | 2016 — 2017

My career began in Archer's Corporate Transactions Group before transferring to Archer's growing Environmental Litigation team.

- Assisted in closing several multi-million dollar transactions.
- Drafted agreement of sale for chain of dance studios and served as primary client contact during transaction.
- Drafted initial corporate documents for start-ups and subsidiaries of existing clients in energy and transportation sectors.

L A U R E N K R O H N

ATTORNEY

SKILLS

| Professional

Legal Project Management
Legal Budgeting
Contractor & Expert Management
Team Building

| Bar Admissions

District of New Jersey
Eastern District of Pennsylvania

REFERENCES

Jack McDermott, Esq.

Archer & Greiner, PC Shareholder T: 215 205 3367 E: jmcdermott@archerlaw.com

Camden Kirkland

Instructor
Penn LPS FinTech Bootcamp
Contact available on request

Judge David Ragonese

N.J. Superior Court

Contact available on request

Judge C. Darnell Jones, II (ret.)

U.S. District Court
District of New Jersey
Contact available on request

WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

STUDENT, FINTECH BOOTCAMP

University of Pennsylvania | January 2022 - August 2022

During the 6-month bootcamp program I worked with different teams to complete 3 professional-level coding projects.

- Passaic River Contamination Visualization created a dashboard showing a sophisticated time-lapse animation of sampling data in the Passaic River over time. Written in Python.
- Sentiment Analysis used natural language processing tools to create a machine learning model that uses the sentiment in SEC 10-k and 10-q reports to predict stock prices. Written in Python.
- Blockchain Trade Tracking created a smart contract and client/server functionality to allow day traders to post their trading positions on the blockchain and gain a subscriber following. Written in Solidity and Python.

CLERKSHIPS

LAW CLERK, HONORABLE DAVID RAGONESE

N.J. Superior Court, Civil Part | 2014 - 2015

STUDENT LAW CLERK, HONORABLE JAMES D. CLYNE (ret.)

Benchmark Resolution Services | 2013 - 2014, 2016

STUDENT LAW CLERK, HONORABLE NOEL HILLMAN

U.S. District Court, D.N.J. | 2014

STUDENT LAW CLERK, HONORABLE C. DARNELL JONES II

U.S. District Court, E.D.Pa. | 2011 - 2012

EXTRA

WILLEM C. VIS INTERNATIONAL COMMERCIAL ARBITRATION MOOT COURT 2012-2014, placed 1^{st} in Munich Moot in 2014.

AYNI COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT, PERU

2010 - 2011, coordinated micro-lending and educational projects.